

ANTHONY PAGE

Senior Sales/Service Associate

Everett, WA 98204 ajisluv@yahoo.com

2533924821

Self motivating sales consultant ready for hire. I am interested in a career in the sales industry with the opportunity for advancement into a management position. I am a natural born leader with the ability to lead by example with little or no supervision. I am proficient in Microsoft Word, Excel, Works, Office and Word Perfect. 10 key adding machine by touch. Typing, 40 WPM.I have also been rated in the top percentile in every sales position I have worked.

#readytowork

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Commercial Account Manager

Panasonic Avionics Corporation - Bothell, WA

December 2019 to April 2020

Account Manager responsible for the management of sales and relationships with particular customers in the Global Airline Industry. Maintains the company's existing relationships, so that they will continue using the company for business. Processed and sold parts requested from customers via email and phone. Processed billing, technical support, returns. Worked in conjunction with the Outside Sales reps to process new orders or generate new business. Utilized multiple applications including Oracle, Excel, Access, Microsoft Windows and Salesforce. Was recently laid off due to loss of business from the Corona Virus Pandemic. Can Supply great references from Management team

Inside Sales Representative

Waste Management - Kirkland, WA March 2019 to January 2020

Manage a high volume of incoming calls from customers while navigating through multiple systems, to answer questions and resolve issues. Excellent customer service, typing, and software skills, are used daily. Communicates concise and accurate information. Establishes customer accounts by negotiating and documenting service type, pricing, billing, and other required information. Listens for and identifies opportunities to cross sell additional products and services. Supports other service lines when required; proficient in multiple queues / service lines.

Inside Sales/Service Representative

Milgard Windows & Doors - Grand Prairie, TX

August 2015 to January 2018

Responsibilities

Inside sales coordinator take inbound calls from future clients interested in quote for windows and doors for both Business and Residential needs. Place orders for Outside sales reps. Make outbound calls to potential clients regarding estimates and offer to upsell or upgrade additional items. Handle all customer service related issues pertaining to billing or breakage, appointments, returns and contracts. Set service appointment for technicians to meet with clients. Multi screen applications, Salesforce, excel, AS400, Microsoft outlook and Internet Explorer

Skills Used

Multi screen applications, Salesforce, excel, AS400, Microsoft outlook and Internet Explorer

Customer Service/Sales Associate

Agero Corp - Irving, TX

September 2011 to January 2014

Inbound customer service rep taking calls that pertain to billing and troubleshooting Hyundai Bluelink and Infiniti Connection telematic systems. Emergency response agent taking incoming SOS calls, Automatic collision notifications, Maintenance Alerts, as well as Enhanced Roadside Assistance. Multi-screen applications and experience in Seibel, AS400, Service Link, Microsoft outlook and Internet Explorer.

Inbound Sales and Service Rep

Terminix - Lewisville, TX

June 2009 to September 2011

Handle incoming calls from customer's interested in pest or termite services. Made outbound calls to customer's to offer pest and termite protection service. Cross sell additional service's to customer's who only took advantage of one service only. One call resolution for customer's who had billing or other customer service issues. Took an average of 100+ calls per day both inbound and outbound. Certified pest and termite technician.

Inbound Sales Agent

Time Warner Cable - Irving, TX March 2008 to March 2009

The Inbound Sales Representative is responsible for driving sales through up-selling and cross selling techniques as well as delivering World Class Service to our customers. •Establishes and maintains World Class levels of customer satisfaction in all sales transactions. •Consistently meets or exceeds weekly and monthly sales activity goals by utilizing sound telephone based selling approaches. •Closes prospective customers using working knowledge of the Time Warner Cable

Insurance Sales Agent

AAA Texas - Irving, TX

products and services.

July 2006 to January 2008

Service and process requests for producer licenses and company appointments within committed service levels/turnaround times

Sell property & casualty financial services products

Handle service issues for agents and monitor status of outstanding issues and requests to ensure that service levels are met in a call center environment

Handle correspondence in a timely manner and assist agents with Internet inquiries

Ensure consistency by staying well- versed in AAA policies and procedures

Ensure accuracy and detail orientation with system notes, compliance, and recordkeeping

Participate in the continuous improvement and definition of customer service processes and procedures

Assure that a professional image is projected in all dealings with internal and external

Senior Sales Consultant

Oreck Corp - New Orleans, LA May 2003 to January 2006

Provided outgoing calls to all potential prospects in the need of home improvements and healthcare. Generated additional leads by providing general consumer information on the importance of proper home healthcare. All calls were generated through EIS and AS400 computer systems. Had to maintain and achieve elevated goal levels. Consistently placed in the top three of all senior sales consultants.

EDUCATION

AA in Business

Nicholls State University - Thibodaux, LA August 1994 to May 1996

Associate in Business

Alabama State University - Montgomery, AL August 1993 to May 1994

SKILLS

- Call Center
- Telesales
- Selling
- Customer Service
- Cold Calling
- Telemarketing
- Quota
- Microsoft Office (10+ years)
- Microsoft Word (10+ years)
- Oracle (5 years)
- Internet Research (10+ years)
- Microsoft Outlook (10+ years)
- Microsoft Access (2 years)
- Excel (5 years)
- B2B
- Account Management (6 years)
- Technical Support (5 years)
- Avionics
- Outbound Sales
- Pest Control
- Inside Sales
- Salesforce
- CRM Software
- Insurance Sales
- Upselling

CERTIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

Driver's License